A Guide to the State Council of Higher Education for Virginia. Office of the Director. Subject and Correspondence Files, 1974-1997
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Materials
  - Council Restructuring, 1994 - 1995 -- fo. 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Donatello Seminar, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Essential Factors of Quality Performance, Cornerstone Management Services (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation Report: State Higher Education Systems and College Completion (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Information on Earle C. Williams, 1993 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Information on Events and Conferences, 1978-1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - New Mexico: State Higher Education Chief and Officers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Pima County (AZ) Community College Leadership Seminar, April 25, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Press Clippings, 1982-1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Response to Higher Education for the 21st Century and The Continuum of Education (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - SB1084: Repeal of 23-9.9 of the Code of Virginia, Jan. 2, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Shenandoah Shakespeare Express (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Business Higher Education Council, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - A Vision of Virginia Higher Education -- draft (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Series VII: Legal Materials
  Arranged by series and follows scheme of arrangement of the series of origin.
  - Subseries 1: Electronic Correspondence, 1986-1995
    - Electronic correspondence, January 4-February 3, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Electronic correspondence, January 15-February 2, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2: Speeches Given by Dr. Davies, 1975-1997
    - Notes for Speeches, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Community College System Leadership Seminar, June 18, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University Mathematics Colloquium, June 26, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Conference on the Academic Profession, Nov. 6, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - North Central Association -- Wingspread Symposium, Nov. 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Community College System Instructional Leadership Seminar, Sept. 23, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Community College System Instructional Leadership Seminar, Aug. 17, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - College of William and Mary, Education in the Commonwealth, Sept. 9, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - VASPA / VACUHO Conference, Dec. 6, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 3: Writings and Publications, 1974-1997
    - How Virginia's Colleges and Universities Can Shape Up the System, Jan. 31, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Book Review: Conflict in Higher Education: State Coordination versus Institutional Independence, by John Millett, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Importance of Being General: Philosophy, Politics, and Institutional Mission Statements, July 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Low priority for state funding: Public colleges at a crossroads, Oct. 11, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Changing the Script: Rethinking Higher Ed, April 12, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Change, yes, but not with a Heavy Hand, Sept. 30, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 4: Source Materials for Writings and Speeches, 1930-1996
    - Articles, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Articles and other materials (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Articles and other materials, oversize (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 5: State of Louisiana, Desegregation Settlement Agreement Monitoring Committee, 1988-1996
    - State of Louisiana, Desegregation Settlement Agreement Monitoring Committee (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 6: Clippings
    - Press clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 7: Gordon K. Davies, dates unknown
    - Listing of articles and speeches (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 8: Miscellaneous Materials
    - Press clippings, 1985-1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)